Father
Папа
The literary part
с поэзией повеселились
Has been lively enough
всё уже было
Why not have some martial arts?
а теперь давай чтонибудь военное
You're being wild
Сумасбродная
No
только
Once you get going
разойдётся
You don't care about anything
уже не остановишь
Alright
Принято
I heard
Говорят
The martial arts in the capital
что в столице боевые мастера
Are quite impressive
не хуже
No less than
чем
Our border troops
наши пограничные воины
I wonder
Не знаю
If there are any masters or heroes
найдётся ли ктото отважный
Willing to spar with me
чтобы скрестить со мной клинки
My second brother
Мой младший брат
Has practiced martial arts since childhood
с детства учился военному делу
And has studied
и знаком с армейскими приёмами
Military techniques
хорошо разбирается
Why not
Почему бы
Have General Zu Yue and second brother
генералу Цзу Юэ не скрестить с младшим братом
Spar
клинки
As entertainment for the general
ради потехи генералу
How about it?
как вам
Prince of Jin
Принц Цзинь
Last time we met
В прошлый раз
I had a mission
я была при исполнении
Mainly won because of numbers
и брала числом
I truly didn't get to experience Your Highness's strength
так и не смогла испытать вашу силу
Today
Сегодня
How about we have a one-on-one match?
как насчёт поединка один на один
All past matters
Всё что было прежде
Your Highness can settle in the match
Ваше Высочество сможете отыграть в поединке